import { Quiz } from './quiz.model';

export const englishQuiz: Quiz[] = [
  {
    name: 'q1',
    question:
      'Malcolm has taken part ... the competition for the tenth consecutive time.',
    responses: ['at', 'in', 'for', 'with'],
    response: 'in',
  },
  {
    name: 'q2',
    question: 'We have ... in-depth research into Molecular Biology.',
    responses: ['did', 'made', 'carried out', 'conduced'],
    response: 'carried out',
  },
  {
    name: 'q3', // 4
    question: '“... do you go to the theatre?” “Once in a blue moon”.',
    responses: ['Whenever', 'How often', 'How about', 'How long'],
    response: 'How often',
  },
  {
    name: 'q4', // 5
    question:
      'If the syllabus ... changed, we would progress in marketing much faster',
    responses: ['is to be', 'has been', 'were', 'be'],
    response: 'were',
  },
  {
    name: 'q5', // 6
    question: 'You can reach me ... 0985/59096378.',
    responses: ['with', 'by', 'in', 'on'],
    response: 'on',
  },
  {
    name: 'q6', // 7
    question: 'It is really not the best way to proceed, ... it?',
    responses: ['won’t', 'is', 'isn’t', 'wasn’t'],
    response: 'is',
  },
  {
    name: 'q7', // 8
    question:
      'I have no time. Well, you are just going to have to ... the time for me then.',
    responses: ['do', 'make', 'have', 'be'],
    response: 'make',
  },
  {
    name: 'q8', // 9
    question: 'Melinda speaks ... ',
    responses: [
      'perfectly Russian',
      'a perfect Russian',
      'Russian perfectly',
      'Russian perfect',
    ],
    response: 'Russian perfectly',
  },
  {
    name: 'q9', // 10
    question:
      'We will have to work ... the cost of going to college very carefully.',
    responses: ['out', 'of', 'off', 'for'],
    response: 'out',
  },
  {
    name: 'q10', // 11
    question: 'I don’t think I have met ... girl as this for a long time.',
    responses: ['as diligent a', 'diligent', 'a diligent', 'as diligent'],
    response: 'as diligent a',
  },
  {
    name: 'q11', // 12
    question: 'Why can’t you stop ... like a child?',
    responses: ['behaving', 'behaved', 'behave', 'to behave'],
    response: 'behaving',
  },
  {
    name: 'q12', // 13
    question: 'I’m sorry but I do not have ... at this point in time.',
    responses: [
      'information',
      'any information',
      'informations',
      'an information',
    ],
    response: 'any information',
  },
  {
    name: 'q13', // 14
    question: 'After making such a mess, ... you could do is tidy up.',
    responses: ['the last', 'the least', 'least', 'the less'],
    response: 'the least',
  },
  {
    name: 'q14', // 15
    question: '“What will you ...?” “A glass of beer, please”',
    responses: ['to drink', 'drinking', 'have', 'have for drink'],
    response: 'have',
  },
  {
    name: 'q15', // 16
    question: 'The car is quite new but is in bad ....',
    responses: ['state', 'condition', 'situation', 'damage'],
    response: 'condition',
  },
  {
    name: 'q16', // 17
    question: 'He’s been living with his father ... his parents divorced.',
    responses: ['until', 'ever more', 'for', 'ever since'],
    response: 'ever since',
  },
  {
    name: 'q17', // 18
    question:
      'A couple have been shot dead in front of their five children by soldiers who fired on the car ... the family was travelling.',
    responses: ['where', 'in which', 'whose', 'in that'],
    response: 'in which',
  },
  {
    name: 'q18', // 19
    question:
      'If you are in search of a bargain at the sales, you ... better get there early.',
    responses: ['should', 'had', 'ought', 'did'],
    response: 'had',
  },
  {
    name: 'q19', // 20
    question: 'I’ll take care of the children while you ... your hair done.',
    responses: ['would get', 'will be getting', 'are getting', 'got'],
    response: 'are getting',
  },
  {
    name: 'q20', // 21
    question: 'His mother ... him €650 to pay for a flight to Beijing',
    responses: ['borrowed', 'charged', 'asked', 'lent'],
    response: 'lent',
  },
];
